Ok. We're going to go ahead and take off the rubber band and we're going to just follow along the line of our part.
Now when it comes to these spiral braids it can be a little bit tricky on keeping your braid centered.
So what we want to do is just make sure we keep grabbing from the outside and then grabbing from the middle.
So right now we're grabbing from the very outside and just adding to it.
But now we want to grab from the stash of hair that's in the middle, just to kind of keep it in line.
And make sure that you're checking the tightness of your braid, that's also very important on keeping it aligned.
But it's just like any other braid, you just grab and go under, you just grab and go under.
And as we'll go back, you see how the braid is staying in the middle.
And we're just going to go along here and create a nice swirl.
The key to this is strictly in the parting.
Once you have that done, you just have to follow along the lines.